Hello friends.  Friends, ICICI LBD has
disclosed its quarter 3 results.  Let's
see what the income
is first.  Before that let me tell you that no
dividend or bonus was issued by the company.
Let's see the income which
was Rs 6582 crore in the last quarter.  Last
year it was Rs 5882 crore.  Now it has become Rs 6610
crore.  There is a jump in income on year on year basis.  If
seen quarter wise, there
is a slight increase from there.  Then let us look at the company
's expenses which were Rs 5830 crore in the last quarter.
Last year it was Rs 5197 crore.  Now it has become
639 crores.  So just as the income has increased, the
company's expenses have also
increased a little.  But expenses
are largely under control.  Then let us see
what the net profit turns out to be.  Which was Rs
819 crore in the last quarter.  Last year it was Rs
724 crore.  Now it has become 658 crores.  If
seen on year on year basis, it is deep there too.   If
seen quarter by quarter, there
is more dip there.  Then let's look at EPS.
In the last quarter it was 16.49, last year it was
14.63, now it is 13.25.  I hope you
found the video inspiring, so please like and subscribe to this channel.  Thank
you.